{"data":[{"question":"Pelican Island in Florida and Oregon Islands in Oregon are wildlife refuges.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Pelican Island ","b":"Florida ","c":"Oregon Islands ","d":"wildlife refuges","answer":"4","explain":"- Wildlife refuges-> wildlife refuge","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"The most coral islands develop from reefs that grow up around volcanic refuges.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"The most ","b":"coral islands ","c":"reefs ","d":"volcanic refuges","answer":"1","explain":"- The most-> most (of)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"The new island of Surtsey is its ideal natural laboratory for scientists.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"The new ","b":"of Surtsey ","c":"its ideal ","d":"for scientists","answer":"3","explain":"- Its ideal-> ideal","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"Coral reefs are limestone formations composed of tiny sea organisms and the remains.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Coral reefs ","b":"limestone formations ","c":"tiny sea organisms ","d":"the remains","answer":"4","explain":"- The remains-> their remains","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"The most of the energy used in our homes and factories is generated from coal, oil, and natural gas   \n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"The most ","b":"the energy ","c":"coal","d":"oil","answer":"1","explain":"- The most-> most of","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"Zachary Taylor was first president to be elected from a State west of the Mississippi River.  \n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"first president ","b":"a State ","c":"west ","d":"the Mississippi River","answer":"1","explain":"- First president-> the first president","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"Old faitful in the Yollowstone National Park is probably the world's most famous  geyser.   \n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Old faitful","b":"the Yollowstone National Park ","c":"the world's ","d":"most famous  ","answer":"2","explain":"- The Yollowston national park-> Yollowston national park","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"The world's fastest animal is cheetah, but if bird are included, the fastest of all  animals is  the spine-tailed swift.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"The world's ","b":"cheetah","c":"the fastest ","d":"the spine-tailed ","answer":"2","explain":"- Cheetah-> the cheetah","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"Soybeans were first grown in the Orient and brought to the Western world during the World War Two.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Soybeans ","b":"the Orient ","c":"the Western ","d":"the  World War  Two ","answer":"4","explain":"- The World war two-> World war two\/ the second world war","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"It is amazing what discovered Faraday in the field of science without the use of  mathematics.     \n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"discovered Faraday ","b":"of science ","c":"without","d":"mathematics","answer":"1","explain":" -> Discovered Faraday-> Faraday discovered","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"}]}